

## CONTACT

nunnapat\_ch@yahoo.com

(786)804-8936

🏠 Miami, FL

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript, React.js, Node.js MongoDB, Express.js, HTML, CSS, SCSS, jQuery, Bootstrap

## **PROJECTS**

The Meteor Game

## https://nunna19.github.io/project-game

A JavaScript game where meteors fall from the sky and the user has to deflect them to save the city.

Technologies Used: JavaScript, Git, Canvas, HTML5, CSS

NaNaWix

#### https://nanawix.herokuapp.com

A web application that allows users to create restaurant websites quickly and easily without prior web development knowledge..

Technologies Used: JavaScript, Node.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, HTML, SASS, CSS, Heroku, PassportJS

**Build-Community** 

#### https://buildcommunity.herokuapp.com

A MERN web application that allows the user to communicate between building management and their tenants more effectively.

Technologies Used: React, JavaScript, Node.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express.js, HTML, SASS, CSS, Heroku, PassportJS

# NUNNAPAT CHIRALERDSITTHIKHUN

https://github.com/nunna19

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nunnapat

### SUMMARY

I'm a recent graduate of Ironhack's Web Development bootcamp in Miami, FL. I have been living here in Miami for 6 years now working as a chef de cuisine, sushi chef and kitchen manager. After working for a few years, I felt the desire to change my career and learn something new. While searching for possibilities, I noticed how attracted to web development I was and decided to embark on my journey of becoming a software engineer.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Kitchen Manager | YuGo sushi burritos, Miami FL | Mar 2015 - Feb 2017

- Responsible for inventory every month and Reduced Food Cost from 55% to 40% by ordering goods and contacting the right suppliers
- In charge of 12 employees' schedules
- Hiring, coaching and training of employees
- Ran the kitchen throughout service and helped the line cooks as needed, ensuring the quality of food and service timing

Head Sushi Chef | Lee Sushi, Miami FL | Mar 2014 - Mar 2015

• Prepped and prepared all menu items to order, menu creation and managed kitchen.

Sushi Chef/Line Cook | Tokyo blue restaurant, Miami FL | June 2013 - Feb 2014

• Prepped and prepared all menu items to order, menu creation and managed kitchen.

Apprentice | Grand Hyatt Erawan Bangkok, Thailand | Nov 2012 - Feb 2013

• Prepared all the food items for buffet, and catered orders for 200+ customer everyday.

#### **EDUCATION**

Ironhack, Miami, FL | 2019 - 2019

Web Development

Ironhack is an immersive bootcamp with locations all over the globe, offering 9-week courses in Full Stack Web Development and UX/UI Design. (400+ hours) - Technologies: JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, HTML and CSS.

Dusit Thani College, Thailand | 2009 - 2013

Bachelor's Degree

Kitchen and Restaurant Management

Nakhonpathom Municipality Vocational College, Thailand | 2005 - 2008

Diploma

Food and Nutrition Program